原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     木淺   Eunice
翻譯     Ethan-澤生
時間軸     少年派
校對     少年派
后期     8T
總監     somehacker  少年派
For centuries, the Order of the Knights Templar...
數個世紀來  圣殿騎士團
have searched for the mythical Apple of Eden.
一直在尋找傳說中的伊甸蘋果
They believe it contains not only
他們相信其中蘊含的
the seeds of man's first disobedience,
不僅是人類第一次違抗命令的種子
but the key to the free will itself.
也是打開自由意志的鑰匙
If they find the relic and decode its secrets,
只要找到遺寶  破解它的秘密
they will have the power to control all freedom of thought.
他們就將擁有控制所有自由思想的力量
Only the brotherhood called the Assassins stands in their way...
刺客兄弟會  是他們唯一的阻礙
西班牙  安達盧西亞  1492年
The Inquisition has finally delivered Spain to the Templars.
宗教裁判所終于將西班牙交給了圣殿騎士團
Sultan Muhammad and his people still hold out in Granada.
穆罕默德蘇丹和他的人還在格拉納達負隅頑抗
But if his son, the prince, is captured,
但如果能抓住他的兒子  他的小王子
he will surrender the city and the Apple of Eden.
他必將獻出城池  還有伊甸蘋果
Do you, Aguilar de Nerha,
你  阿圭拉·德·納哈
swear to honor our order in the fight for freedom?
是否起誓在自由之戰中守護我們的刺客兄弟會
To defend mankind against Templars' tyranny,
為了人類抵抗圣殿騎士團的暴政
and preserve free will?
守護自由意志
I swear.
我起誓
If the Apple falls into their hands,
如果伊甸蘋果落入他們之手
the Templars will destroy everything that stands in their way.
圣殿騎士團將毀滅一切阻礙
Protest, dissent, our right to think for ourselves.
抗議  反對  自由思考是我們的權利
Swear to me that you will sacrifice your life
向我起誓  哪怕犧牲你自己的
and lives of everyone here to keep it from them.
甚至這里所有人的性命  也不會令其落入他們之手
Yes, Mentor.
遵命  師父
Our lives are nothing.
我們的生命不重要
The Apple is everything.
伊甸蘋果才是一切
The spirit of the Eagle, will watch over the future.
雄鷹之靈  將守護我們的未來
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
所有人都盲目追尋著真相時
remember, nothing is true.
謹記  一切皆虛
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
所有人都被道德或法律束縛時
remember, everything is permitted.
謹記  無事不允
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我們在黑暗中侍奉光明
We are Assassins.
我們  是刺客
刺客信條
墨西哥  下加州  1986年
Shit!
媽的
Mom?
媽媽
Dad?
爸爸
Your blood is not your own, Cal.
你的生命不是你個人的  卡爾
They've found us.
他們找到我們了
Live in the shadows.
要活在暗處
Go! Go now!
走  快走
30年后
美國德州  亨茨維爾監獄
You're here to save my soul.
你是來拯救我的靈魂的
Something like that.
差不多吧
I...
我
I understand it is your birthday.
我了解到今天是你生日
Yeah.
是啊
The party is just getting started.
生日派對正要開始呢
Sit down. You're making me nervous.
坐下  你讓我緊張
Lord, wash away my sin,
主啊  洗刷我的罪孽
and I will be clean, once again.
我將重新潔凈
You're not much for the Bible, are you?
你不怎么信《圣經》  是嗎
Be it known that Callum Lynch
卡勒姆·林奇
has been found guilty of capital murder
被判謀殺罪  將于今日
and sentenced to die on this day, October 21st 2016.
即2016年10月21日  執行死刑
Does the prisoner wish to make a final statement?
囚犯有什么遺言嗎
Tell my father that I'll see him in hell.
請轉告我父親  就說我們地獄再見
My name is Dr. Sophia Rikkin.
我叫索菲婭·萊肯
At 6 P.M. yesterday evening, you were executed
昨晚6點整  你被執行死刑
and pronounced dead.
并宣布死亡
And so far, as anyone in the world knows or cares,
現在  對這世上任何認識你或在乎你的人來說
you no longer exist.
你已經不存在了
It's better you to sit.
你最好還是坐著
My eyes...
我的眼睛...
What are you feeling right now is normal and uncomfortable.
你現在的感覺很正常  雖然不舒服
Cal.
卡爾
I'm here to help you.
我是來幫你的
And you're here to help me.
你也要幫助我
Let him go.
讓他走
Don't touch him.
別碰他
Go ahead. Do it.
來啊  勇敢去做啊
Jump.
跳啊
You are not a prisoner here, Cal.
你在這里不是囚犯  卡爾
I'm here to protect you.
我是來保護你的
If you listen to me, everything is going to make sense.
如果你認真聽我的話  慢慢你就會明白一切
And you need to trust me.
而且你得信任我
Where am I?
我在哪兒
You're in a rehabilitation wing of abstergo Foundation in Madrid,
你在馬德里阿布斯泰戈基金會的康復區
a private organization dedicated to the perfection of human kind.
一個致力于實現完美人類的私人機構
With your help, we can pioneer new ways
有你的幫助  我們就能開辟新途徑
to eradicate violence.
最終消除暴力
I had this.
我可以搞定的
Your father wants him in.
你父親命令帶他回去
He's my patient. This is my program.
他是我的病人  這是我的項目
Prepare the Animus.
準備阿尼姆斯
- Are the blades prepared? - Right here.
-刺客之刃準備好了嗎  -就在這兒
- And we confirmed their provenance? - They belong to Aguilar.
-刺客之刃主人確定了嗎  -是阿圭拉的
We recovered them from his burial site.
是從他的墳墓找回的
What are these?
這是什么
Assume final preparations.
最后階段準備
Our regression, Andalusia, 1492.
回溯坐標  1492年  安達盧西亞
Record everything.
完整記錄下來一切
Arms ready.
機械臂準備完畢
What is this?
這是怎么回事
I'm sorry, Cal, this is not the way I like to do things.
抱歉  卡爾  我也不喜歡用這種方式
Then don't do it.
那就別這么做
Insert epidural.
進行硬膜外麻醉注射
What do you want from me?
你到底想從我身上得到什么
Your past.
你的過去
Listen to me carefully, Cal.
認真聽我說  卡爾
You're about to enter the Animus.
你即將進入阿尼姆斯
What you are about to see, hear and feel,
你將看到的  聽到的  感到的一切
are the memories of someone who has been dead for 500 years.
都是一個已經死去五百年之人的記憶
Wait a minute.
等等
You can't change what happens, Cal.
你無法抵抗的  卡爾
Engage scanner.
啟動掃描設備
Status?
狀態如何
Scanning DNA chains. Searching for time frame.
掃描DNA鏈  正在搜索時間幀
First memory match locked.
第一匹配記憶已鎖定
DNA match identified.
匹配DNA已識別
Stay with it, Cal.
不要抵抗  卡爾
Attempt synchronization.
嘗試同步
We found him.
找到他了
We found Aguilar.
我們找到了阿圭拉
Synchronization achieved.
同步達成
There.
好了
Commence regression.
啟動回溯
Our mission is the boy.
我們的任務是找到那孩子
It's the prince.
是王子
Which household harbored the boy?
是誰家藏匿了這個孩子
Only me.
只有我
Nobody else knew. Nobody.
其他人都不知道  沒人知道
Hang his family and make him watch.
絞死他的家人  讓他看著
Burn the whole village.
燒掉整個村子
With the prince of Granada as captive, his father, Sultan,
有格拉納達王子做人質  他父親蘇丹
will surrender his rebellious city,
將獻出叛軍城池
the last safe haven for the infidels.
那是異教徒的最后避風港
God will punish his people's heresy.
上帝將懲罰他們信奉的異教
Finally Spain will be under one Templar rule.
西班牙終于要臣服于圣殿騎士團之統治
Stay with the memory, Cal.
跟著記憶走  卡爾
Aguilar! The boy, Aguilar! The boy!
阿圭拉  那孩子  阿圭拉  孩子
Aguilar, the boy!
阿圭拉  孩子
Pull him!
把他拉回來
Commence rehabilitation.
啟動復原
Run a system's check, and log his condition.
進行系統檢查  記錄他的情況
You did well, Cal.
你做得很好  卡爾
Looking back it's clear that
回顧歷史  很明確的一點就是
a history of the world is history a violence.
世界歷史就是一部暴力史
Last year the economic impact of
去年的反社會行為
antisocial behavior was 9 trillion dollars.
對經濟造成的損失高達9萬億美元
We believe that man today experiences a measure of aggression
我們認為現代人總會有一些暴力沖動
for which he finds no acceptable outlets.
但卻找不到合適的宣泄方式
Now imagine
想象一下
if all these costs could be channeled elsewhere...
如果這些代價  可以在別的地方得到管控...
So regression went well?
回溯進行得順利嗎
Lynch is the one.
就是林奇
Direct descendent of Aguilar.
他是阿圭拉的直系后裔
Everything was clear in there, for the first time.
一切都清晰了起來  這可是第一次
What do we all dream of?
我們共同的夢想是什么
A more peaceful world.
就是一個更和平的世界
I see you stole my lines again.
你又盜用我的演講辭
I only steal from the best.
我只盜用最出色的人
And the artifact?
那件寶物呢
The Apple. It's within our grasp.
伊甸蘋果  唾手可得
What happened in there?
在里面發生了什么
Why did you pull him?
你為什么將他拉回來了
I had to.
我必須如此
We have to keep him healthy.
我們要保護他的安全
Earn his confidence.
贏得他的信任
And I know that will lead us to it.
我確信他能帶領我們找到寶物
Push him.
對他狠點
That's not how the Animus works.
阿尼姆斯的運作方式不是這樣的
Here you go.
好了
Thank you.
謝謝
1917 Rutherford splits the atom.
1917年  盧瑟福分裂開了原子
1953 Watson and Crick find a double helix.
1953年  沃森和克里克發現雙螺旋
2016 my daughter,
2016年  我的女兒
finds the cure for violence.
找到了根除暴力的方法
You've always been brighter than me.
你向來都比我聰明
I'm late.
我要遲到了
I have to report to the Elders.
我還得向長老會匯報
Francisco Rizi's Grand Inquisition.
弗朗西斯科·利茲的《宗教裁判所大法官》
1492.
1492年
War, religious prosecution,
戰爭  宗教迫害
and the closest Father Torquemada or any of our Order
也是托爾克馬達法官及騎士團成員
came to a finding the Apple of Eden.
尋找伊甸蘋果最接近成功的一次了
How are you, my friend?
你還好嗎  朋友
Well.
很好
Your Excellency.
大人
Next week when the Elders meet,
下周  等長老們會面
we shall vote to discontinue your Abstergo project.
我們會就是否中斷你的阿布斯泰戈項目進行投票
We feel that giving you 3 billion annually,
我們覺得  每年給你的三十億資金
could be better spent elsewhere.
花在別處會有更大的用途
Tri billion is nothing compared to...
三十億相比...
We've won.
我們勝利了
People are no longer care about their civil liberties,
人們已經不在乎他們的公民自由了
they care about their standard of life.
他們只在乎自己的生活水平
The modern world has outgrown notions like freedom.
現代世界已經拋棄自由這種理念了
They are content to follow.
他們樂于盲從
The threat remains while free will exists.
只要自由意志尚存  威脅就依然存在
For centuries we try with religion,
數個世紀以來  我們試圖通過宗教
with politics and now consumerism to eliminate dissent.
政治  以及現在的消費主義  來鏟除異議
Isn't it the time we gave a science a try?
現在難道不是時候嘗試科學辦法了嗎
My daughter is closer than we've ever been.
我女兒比我們所有人都要更接近成功了
How is your beautiful daughter?
你美麗的女兒怎么樣了
She has traced protectors of the Apple.
她追蹤到了伊甸蘋果的守護者
Where?
在哪兒
Andalucia, 1492.
安達盧西亞  1492年
The descendents?
他們的后人呢
All the blood lines have died out.
所有的后人都死光了
But one.
只剩下一個
We've traced his back 500 years,
我們追蹤他的血脈到500年前
to the Assassin's Brotherhood.
定位到刺客兄弟會身上
Hallucinations are what we call the "Bleeding effect."
幻覺  就是我們所謂的"血緣效應"
Images of your regression,
回溯后的畫面
laying themselves over your present day field of vision.
潛藏在你現在的視界里
If you allow me, I can teach you how to control them.
如果你允許的話  我可以教你怎么控制它們
Stand down. I have this.
退下  我可以搞定
Let her be.
隨她去吧
What is it? The machine?
那臺機器  到底是什么東西
It's genetic memory.
那是基因記憶機器
By using the Animus,
通過使用阿尼姆斯
we can relive lives of those who made us who we are.
我們可以獲取祖先的記憶
What I saw in there, it felt real.
我看到的情形  感覺很真實
It was.
的確如此
In a way.
在某種程度上是
Don't mess with me!
別跟我耍花招
I feel different now.
我現在感覺不一樣了
Why the aggression?
為什么這么有攻擊性
I'm an aggressive person.
我本就是個有攻擊性的人
What kind of prison is this?
這是什么監獄
It's not a prison, Cal.
這里不是監獄  卡爾
You'll learn more if you cooperate.
只要你乖乖合作  就會了解到更多東西
Let me go.
放開我
I'm hungry.
我餓了
Come with me.
跟我來
林奇
1979年-現在
對卡勒姆·林奇的擔憂加深
黑幫突襲當地辦事處
林奇必死無疑
What is this?
這是什么東西
I know everything about you, Cal.
我知道關于你的一切  卡爾
Your medical data, your psychological profile,
你的醫療數據  你的心理檔案
the mutations in your MAO-A gene.
以及你MAO-A基因的變異
I know about the foster homes.
我知道你在寄養家庭的事
The juvenile homes.
在少管所的事
You are a living proof of the link between heredity and crime.
你是遺傳和犯罪存在關聯的活生生的證據
How did you find me?
你們是怎么找到我的
We found Aguilar.
我們先找到了阿圭拉
When you were arrested, your DNA matched his.
你被逮捕時  你的DNA被發現與他的相匹配
- Who is Aguilar? - Your ancestor.
-阿圭拉是誰  -你的祖先
His family were Assassins.
他的家族祖上都是刺客
They were burnt at the stake by the Templars,
他們被圣殿騎士團  托爾克馬達  和你看到的
Torquemada and the black knight you saw, Ojeda.
那個黑衣騎士奧哈達綁在柱子上燒死了
Aguilar took up the Assassins' cause.
阿圭拉繼承了刺客大業
Do you go out much?
你經常外出嗎
More than you.
比你外出的時候多
And the others in here? Are they the lab rats too?
這里的其他人呢  也都是實驗室里的小白鼠嗎
They are Assassins, murderers like their ancestors.
他們也是刺客  跟他們的祖先一樣都是殺手
Like you, Cal.
跟你一樣  卡爾
All born with predisposition to violence.
天生就具有暴力傾向
Murderer?
殺手
- You killed the man. - A pimp.
-你殺了那個人  -他是個皮條客
Would you kill again?
你會再次殺人嗎
Happy families.
幸福的一家人
She must be very proud.
她一定為你感到很驕傲
I wouldn't know.
我不知道
She was killed by an Assassin.
她被一名刺客殺死了
Like your mother.
跟你母親的遭遇一樣
Sorry.
抱歉
My old man killed my mother.
我父親殺了我母親
And how does that make you feel?
那讓你是什么感覺
Like killing him.
我想殺了他
Either we let it to effect us for the rest of our lives,
要么我們讓這事影響我們一輩子
or we just do something about it.
要么采取點措施
You turn to violence, I turn to science.
你選擇了暴力  我選擇了科學
It's the Apple of Eden, Cal.
那是伊甸蘋果  卡爾
I believe it exists.
我相信它真的存在
The Bible tells us
《圣經》告訴我們
it contained the seed of man's first disobedience.
其中蘊含了人類第一次違抗命令的種子
But there are those of us who believe that
但也有些人認為
God or some ancient civilization
上帝  或某種古文明
have left us a road map
給我們留下了一張指示圖
to understand why people are violent.
幫助我們了解人為什么會有暴力性
Aguilar was the last person known to have had it in his possession.
據稱伊甸蘋果最后一次出現是在阿圭拉手上
We need you to find out where he hid it.
我們需要你查出他把那東西藏在哪兒了
I thought I was here to be cured.
我以為我是來接受治療的
Violence is a disease.
暴力就是一種疾病
Like cancer.
跟癌癥一樣
And like cancer, we hope to control it one day.
并且如同癌癥  我們希望有一天能控制住它
Violence is what kept me alive.
正是暴力讓我活到了今天
Well technically, you're dead.
嚴格來說  你已經死了
I'm hungry.
我餓了
What's in it for me?
我能得到什么好處
Once my research is complete,
一旦我的研究完成了
there is no reason to keep you here.
就沒必要把你關在這里了
I get my life back?
我能過上以前的生活
Better. A new one.
更好  你能擁有全新的生活
You are hungry.
你不是餓了嗎
You don't know who he is, what he is.
你不知道他是什么人  也不清楚他的本性
He is a dangerous man.
他是個危險人物
Give him little more time, Emir.
再給他點時間  埃米爾
Man may prove that has some noble blood in him yet.
那家伙可能會證明  他身上有高貴的血統
How about here, sir?
不如坐這里吧  先生
It's an open menu, but we do recommend a chicken.
菜單上有很多可選項  但我們推薦雞肉
What can I get you, Mr. Lynch? It's an open menu,
你需要什么  林奇先生  菜單上有很多可選項
but we do recommend a chicken.
但我們推薦雞肉
I'll steak.
我要牛排
Steak for the pioneer.
給這位先驅來份牛排
Who are you?
你是誰
They call me Moussa.
他們都叫我穆薩
But my name is Baptiste. I'm dead 200 years now.
但我的真名叫巴普蒂斯特  我已經死了200年了
Voodoo poisoner.
巫毒大師
I'm harmless.
我是無害的
They're watching you.
他們都在觀察你
Waiting to see who you are, pioneer.
等著看你是什么樣的人  先驅
Have you met him yet?
你見過他了嗎
We are the last to protect the Apple, my friend.
我們是伊甸蘋果最后的守護者  朋友
Pick the wrong choice,
你一旦做出錯誤的選擇
you'll send us all to infinity.
就會把我們全部打入無限時空
This...
這個
belongs to you.
屬于你
You're going to lead them right to it.
你要帶領他們找到伊甸蘋果
No, I'm going to eat it.
不  我會把蘋果吃掉
What the fuck is going on?
到底怎么回事
He has to go back in the Animus.
他必須再次進入阿尼姆斯
Now.
馬上
He needs more time before he goes in again.
他需要休息一段時間  才能再次進入
We don't have time.
我們沒時間了
Why?
為什么
I won't risk his life.
我不會拿他的生命冒險
I'll have to find someone else to do it.
那我只好找其他人代勞了
You're up, slugger.
到你了  猛男
I'm crazy.
我瘋了
Crazy for feeling so lonely.
瘋狂想感覺如此孤寂
They're getting him back in again.
他們打算把他再次送進阿尼姆斯
We should stop him before he betrays us.
我們應該在他背叛我們之前阻止他
Set the date for the six.
設置好中斷日期
If his condition deteriorates, pull him out.
如果他的情況惡化  就把他拉出來
- You father... - I don't care what my father said.
-你父親說...  -我不管他說過什么
What in the world did I do?
我到底做錯了什么
- Cal, listen to me. - I'm crazy for trying...
-卡爾  聽我說  -我瘋狂嘗試...
Listen to me. You have to stay with Aguilar.
聽我說  你必須跟阿圭拉保持合體狀態
Crazy for crying...
瘋狂想哭泣...
Staying in synch-void could be dangerous.
脫離同步狀態可能會有危險
And I'm crazy for loving you...
我瘋狂地愛著你...
Soon they will march on Granada.
很快他們將進軍格拉納達
Sultan Muhammad is weak.
默罕默德蘇丹王很軟弱
He'll surrender the Apple
他為了救王子
and betray the Creed to save the prince.
肯定會交出蘋果  背叛信條
The love makes us weak.
愛讓我們軟弱
Gladly I'll sacrifice my flesh and blood,
我愿意犧牲自己的親骨肉
for survival of the Creed.
換取信條永存
When I die today, don't waste your tears for me.
我今日若死  你無需為我落淚
The Lord spoke.
主已給出指示
And he said:
他說
"If a man abide not in me
"一個人若不住在我里面
he is cast into the fire
他就會被丟進火里
and he is burned!"
被焚燒殆盡"
For decades,
數十年以來
you have lived in the world torn apart
你們都活在因宗教紛爭
by religious discord.
而分崩離析的世界
But soon, thanks to God
但不久之后  多虧上帝
and Inquisition
和宗教裁判所
we will purge this disease!
我們將徹底清除這種疾病
The sinners before you,
在你們面前的罪人
sought to defend the heretic prince of Granada,
企圖保護格拉納達的異教王子
the last heathen stronghold in our holy war.
那里是圣戰要攻下的最后一個異教徒據點
So today,
所以今天
before our king and queen
在國王和王后的見證下
I swear we shall wash ourselves clean,
我發誓  我們都將在上帝的圣火中
in the holy fire of God!
洗凈污穢
Behold...
看啊
God's will!
上帝的旨意
You will watch your mentor burn
你將眼睜睜看著你的師父被燒死
and then you will die the slowest.
然后你也將受盡折磨而死
Give glory to the future.
將榮耀歸于未來
Not to us.
而不是我們
He is synchronizing.
他正在同步
Damned heretics!
該死的異教徒
Don't let them escape!
別讓他們跑了
Jump.
跳啊
Complete desynch.
解除同步完成
Get him down!
放他下來
Call the medics!
快叫醫護人員來
Okay. It's okay. Cal, stay with me. Cal.
沒事了  卡爾  堅持住  卡爾
Stay... It's okay. Hurry up!
堅持住  沒事了  快點
Okay. Okay. Look at me.
沒事了  看著我
Look at me.
看著我
I can't feel my legs.
我的腿失去知覺了
Paralysis is temporal.
身體麻痹只是暫時的
What's the bad news?
壞消息是什么
It caused a neurological split but we got you through it.
它引起了神經分裂  但我們把你治好了
This time.
這一次僥幸而已
I'm gonna die in here, aren't I?
我會死在這里的  對吧
No.
不
Not if you go in there on your own free will.
如果你憑借你的自由意志進去  就不會死
I can't do this.
我做不到
Yes, you can.
你可以的
The Apple. You're the only one left who can find it.
能找到伊甸蘋果的人只剩下你了
We can put an end to pain, Cal.
我們能結束痛苦  卡爾
For everyone.
幫助所有人
Where did you get this?
你從哪里找到的
My father recovered it from the scene of your mother's murder.
我父親在你母親的兇殺現場找到的
And brought it here for safekeeping.
然后帶到這里來保管
Safekeeping?
保管
You stole it.
你們這是偷竊
It's your mother's necklace. I wanted you to have it.
這是你母親的項鏈  我想交給你
Why was he there?
他為什么會去那里
- To save her. - From whom?
-去救她  -誰要害她
- Her own people. - What's that got to do with you?
-她的同僚  -那跟你有什么關系
Assassins and Templars have been at war for centuries.
刺客和圣殿騎士已經交戰了數個世紀
I aim to change that.
我希望能改變這局面
That's right, I forgot.
對哦  我忘了
We're here to combat aggression.
我們的目的是根除暴力
I don't think I like your methods.
我不喜歡你的方式
I am a scientist.
我是一個科學家
I'm here to be cured of violence.
我來這里是為了治好我暴力的一面
Who's gonna cure you?
但有誰能治好你呢
We're feeding the beast.
我們是在喂養一頭野獸
We're making him stronger.
我們在使他變得愈發強大
I am Dr Rikkin.
我是萊肯博士
Alan.
叫我亞倫吧
I look after things here in Abstergo.
我負責管理阿布斯泰戈
You like to keep things in the family, huh?
你不喜歡讓外人插手  對吧
Yes.
沒錯
I'm sorry if we caused you any discomfort.
如果我們給你造成不適  很抱歉
Is there anything I can do?
有什么需要我幫忙的嗎
How about you let me out of here?
讓我離開這里怎么樣
That's something I can't manage.
這件事我辦不到
I'm here to make a deal.
我是來跟你做一筆交易的
We need the Apple.
我們需要伊甸蘋果
And we need you to get it for us.
也需要你幫我們找到它
You've been desynching in the Animus.
你在阿尼姆斯里一直在解除同步
We need you not to do that.
請你不要再那樣做
Sending me back to the machine?
又要把我送進那臺機器里了嗎
No, you've already shown us what we needed to see.
不  你已經讓我們看到我們需要看到的情形了
Will you let us free then?
那你會釋放我們嗎
What do you hope to gain from the newcomer?
你希望從那個新人身上得到什么
Something that'll benefit us all.
能讓所有人都受益的東西
You too, Moussa.
包括你  穆薩
What have you done to them?
你對他們做了什么
It's what happens
如果你用自己的意志
if you don't enter in regression on your own volition.
進行時空回溯  就會產生這種后果
Do you recognize this?
你認識這個嗎
It's Assassin's blade.
這是刺客之刃
This is the actual one...
你父親正是用這把刀
your father used to take your mother's life.
奪去了你母親的生命
He's here, you know?
他也在這里  你知道嗎
Mother's death, Cal.
一個母親的死亡  卡爾
Not something a boy should ever be made to see.
永遠不該讓她兒子看到
This is wrong.
這樣做不對
You left me no choice.
是你讓我別無選擇
He has to go in on his own free will, you said that.
他一定要靠自己的自由意志進去  是你說的
- I had to negotiate. - You mean manipulate?
-我只能去協商  -你是指操縱吧
I assured the Elders we would have the Apple for London.
我向長老們承諾了我們會把伊甸蘋果送到倫敦
That's in two days.
只剩下兩天時間了
He doesn't want to know his past, or his father.
他不想知道自己的過去  也不想認識自己的父親
He wants to destroy them, both.
他想毀掉這兩樣東西
We're not in the business of creating monsters.
我們不是在制造怪物
We neither created them nor destroyed them.
我們沒有制造它們  也沒有毀掉它們
We merely abandoned them to their own inexorable faith.
我們不過是將它們拋向自己必然的信念
- You're your mother's son. - What does that mean?
-你是你母親的孩子  -什么意思
Blood that flows through you is not your own.
你體內的血液不屬于你自己
Belongs to the Creed.
而屬于信條
Your mother knew that.
你母親深知這一點
She died so the Creed may live.
她用死換來信條的傳承
Remind me how, exactly!
告訴我到底是怎么回事
What you saw, I did.
你看到的事  是我干的
You murdered her.
你殺了她
I took her life rather than have it stolen by that machine.
我殺了她  總比讓那臺機器弄死她要好
Man grows with the greatness of his task.
人因其崇高的使命而成長
I ought to have killed you.
我應該把你也殺了
I couldn't.
我下不了手
Well, here.
給你
Take it.
拿著
Do what you couldn't do 30 years ago.
完成你30年前沒能做到的事
It's in your hands now, Cal.
如今刺客之刃已在你手中  卡爾
This is what they want.
這正是他們想要的結果
Spill my blood.
殺了我
But do not go back in the Animus.
但千萬不要再進入阿尼姆斯
Why?
為什么
The Apple contains the genetic code for free will.
伊甸蘋果當中蘊含著自由意志的基因密碼
They will use it to destroy us.
他們會用來毀滅我們
I'm gonna find it.
我一定會找到的
And watch them destroy you and your Creed.
然后看著他們  毀掉你和你的信條
You can not kill the Creed.
信條是殺不死的
It's in your blood.
它根植于你的血液中
The Apple is everything.
伊甸蘋果就是一切
Your mother died to protect it.
你母親為了保護它犧牲了生命
She had no choice.
她當年別無選擇
I do.
但我有
You're gonna kill the Creed!
你要殺了信條
Take me to the Animus.
帶我去阿尼姆斯
Put me in.
把我放進去
Prepare the Animus.
準備阿尼姆斯
Voluntary regression.
自愿回溯
Do you know how the Assassins came to be named?
你知道殺手的名字是怎么得來的
From an Arabic word "Hashashin".
是根據阿拉伯詞語"哈薩辛"演變來的
They were society's outcasts.
他們曾是社會的棄徒
Those who stole, who murdered in cold blood.
他們會偷盜  冷血地殺人
People ridiculed them... Rebels, fools, drug addicts.
人們都嘲弄他們  叛黨  白癡  癮君子
But they were wise.
但其實他們很明智
They used this reputation to hide the dedication to principles
他們利用這種罵名  來隱藏自身對信條的忠貞
beyond those of even their strongest enemies.
甚至瞞過了最強大的敵人
And for that I admire them.
為此  我很欽佩他們
But you're not one of those men.
但你不是其中的一員
Are you?
對吧
Let's find out.
那就試試看吧
Commencing regression.
開始回溯
This is my life's work.
這是我畢生的事業
It's my life.
這是我的生命
For the Creed.
為了信條
Our own lives...
我們自身的生命
What matters is what we leave behind.
重要的是  我們為后世留下什么
Sultan...
蘇丹
Surrender the Apple.
把伊甸蘋果交出來
Your Assassin protectors are gone.
那些保護你的刺客都已經走了
The Creed is finished.
信條已經完了
My son.
我兒
Here lies the seed of man's first disobedience,
這里面是人類第一次違抗命令的種子
of free will itself.
是自由意志
Thanks to the Apple of Eden,
多虧了伊甸蘋果
the known world
這已知的世界
shall be ushered into a new age.
將會被引入新紀元
One of peace,
一個和平的新紀元
in which all the warring populations of mankind
在那里  所有彼此敵對的人類
shall bow in perfect obedience to our one templar rule.
將完全服從圣殿的統治
The Apple.
伊甸蘋果
Give it to him.
交給他
Now.
立刻
For the Creed.
為了信條
Go!
快走
Forgive me.
原諒我
It's over!
已經結束了
Assassin!
有刺客
A leap of faith.
信仰之躍
Where are we?
現在在哪兒
It looks like a military port.
似乎是個軍事港口
Kadiz, Palos de la Frontera.
位于加的斯  帕洛斯德拉夫龍特拉
The Assassins died for it.
刺客為此而死
Protect it with your life.
用你的生命去保護它
I am a friend of the Creed.
我是信條的朋友
Take it to your grave.
帶入你的墳墓
I swear.
我發誓
What is it? Translation.
他們在說什么  翻譯一下
Following the light of the sun,
追尋著太陽的光芒
I shall leave this old world behind.
我將拋下這個舊世界
It's Christopher Columbus.
是克里斯托弗·哥倫布
Where is he buried?
他的墳墓在哪里
His remains were returned to Spain.
他的遺體被轉送回了西班牙
His tomb is in Seville Cathedral.
他的墳墓在塞維利亞大教堂里
We found it.
我們找到了
Hey All Stars, come here.
全明星們  過來
Pick one.
挑一個
Anyone.
隨便選一個
- Breach in common room. - Seal the Animus.
-休息大廳發生襲擊事件  -封鎖阿尼姆斯
Is it a memory?
那是記憶嗎
No.
不是
Come on!
快啊
- Transport? - Standing by.
-傳輸裝置如何了  -準備就緒
Protect the Animus. Purge the facility.
保護好阿尼姆斯  肅清整個機構
I need to get you out of here first.
我需要先把你救出去
- No! - We have to leave, Sophia.
-不行  -我們必須走了  索菲婭
No!
不
不要
You are not alone, Cal.
你不是一個人  卡爾
You never were.
你從來都不是
- Open... - Come on.
-開門  -快
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
所有人都盲目追尋著真相時
- remember... - Nothing is true.
-記住  -一切皆虛
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
所有人都被道德或法律束縛時
- remember... - Everything is permitted.
-記住  -無事不允
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我們在黑暗中侍奉光明
We are Assassins.
我們是刺客
What now, pioneer?
現在要怎樣  先驅
We fight.
我們要戰斗
Your Excellency.
大人
The glory will go to your father.
榮譽將屬于你父親
But we both know who found it.
但我們都知道是誰找到的
Your time will come, my child.
屬于你的光輝時刻會到來的  孩子
倫敦  圣殿大廳
They'll give you a Nobel peace prize for this.
他們會為此把諾貝爾和平獎頒給你
You better start writing your speech.
你最好開始寫演講辭了
- I've read yours. - And?
*-我看過你的演講辭了  -然后呢
If we eradicate free will, we eradicate the Assassins.
如果我們鏟除了自由意志  就將刺客兄弟會消滅了
A cancer that has menaced society for centuries.
他們就像是荼毒社會長達數個世紀的癌癥
It's not my best work, but it gets the point across.
那不是我的最佳作品  但意思都表達清楚了
We've been looking for solutions.
我們一直在尋找解決辦法
You've eliminated the problem.
你解決了這個問題
So my program...
所以我的項目...
Has brought order to society for the first time.
第一次為這個社會帶來了秩序
I'm accountable for this.
這一切都是我的功勞
You've already been accounted for.
已經算上你的功勞了
Our work belongs to the Elders.
我們的成果都屬于長老會
This is their finest hour.
現在是他們最光榮的時刻
You lied to me.
你對我撒謊了
I've always known
我一直都知道
that in your heart you're a scientist first, templar second.
在你心里  科學排第一位  圣殿騎士團排第二
Your recent work has impressed as much
你最近的工作實在太令人嘆為觀止了
but it has confirmed our belief
但那恰恰證實了我們的信仰
that mankind cannot be redeemed.
也就是人類是無法獲得救贖的
So you've thought of everything.
所以你早就盤算好了一切
Not quite. My speech.
也不算吧  我的演講辭就沒想好
It could do with one of your elegant openings.
如果能加上你出色的開場白就更好了
Now I've become death,
現在我成了死神
the destroyer of worlds.
世界的毀滅者
Not sure that I could make that work.
不太確定我能否讓這一切實現
It is with great pleasure tonight that I introduce
今晚  我很榮幸地向大家介紹
the architect of our ancient order's future.
我們古老騎士團的未來的構建者
Please welcome the CEO of Abstergo Foundation,
有請阿布斯泰戈基金會的總裁
Dr. Alan Rikkin.
亞倫·萊肯博士
With the recovery of the Apple,
隨著伊甸蘋果被重新尋回
we are now in possession
我們現在擁有了
of the complete genetic road map to humanity's instincts.
關于人類本能的完整基因地圖
Any impulse towards independence,
任何能導致獨立
resistance or rebellion will be crushed.
抗拒或反叛的沖動  都將被清除
Any predisposition that might oppose our march of progress
任何違背人類進步的體征
can now be eradicated.
現在都能被根除
All I have to do is shout.
我只需大喊一聲  你就會沒命
I'm here to help you.
我是來幫助你的
And you're here to help me.
你也是來幫助我的
I can't help you anymore.
我幫不了你了
What about all those great plans?
那么那些偉大的計劃呢
Cure violence, combat aggression.
治愈暴力  攻擊性行為
That's not going to happen.
那是不可能的了
You've started this, Sophie. You don't get to walk away.
是你開啟的這一切  索菲  你不能轉身離開
We both know what happens next.
我們都知道接下來會怎樣
Not everything deserves to live.
并非所有東西都有資格活著
I can't do this.
我做不到
Yes, you can.
不  你可以的
But it is not to ourselves,
但我們不該將榮耀
but to the future, that we must give glory.
獻給自己  而是應該獻給未來
A future purged of the Assassin's Creed!
一個沒有刺客信條的未來
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士們先生們
the Apple of Eden.
這就是伊甸蘋果
I did this.
是我干的
I will retrieve the artifact for the Elders.
我會替長老會尋回寶物
Lynch I want for me.
但我想把林奇留給自己
It is not to ourselves,
但我們不該將榮耀
but to the future, that we must give glory.
獻給自己  而是應該獻給未來